Guide to the Deane W. Malott papers, 1951-1964
Malott, Deane W. papers, 1951-1964
- Academic Freedom, Clippings, etc., 1951-53 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  Konvitz, Milton R.; Dodds, Harold W.; Emanuel, Victor. Association of American Universities; Harvard University.
- Campus Organizations and New Outlets., 1951-53 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  Burgholder, Edwin V.
- Campus Publications., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  Adams, Bristow. "Cornell Widow."
- Gripes of Various Kinds., 1952 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Committee on the Size of the University., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Cabinet Meeting Minutes., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  McCambridge, Robert H.
- Committee to Study Faculty Advisory Systems., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Cabinet Meeting Minutes., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Communism, Faculty., 1951-54 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Morrison, Philip; Steinmetz, Harry C.; Henriksen, Erik K.; Singer, Marcus. "Why Don't You Do Something About Professor X?" by DWM.
- Communism, Faculty., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Singer, Marcus; Tuller, J. D.; Feldman, Harold; Burgum, Edwin Berry; Brewer, R. Selden; Evans, M. O.; Dean, Daniel; Aasgaard, A. O.; Emanuel, Victor. "Counterattack."
- Communism, Faculty., 1952-53 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Emanuel, Victor; Biggerstaff, Knight; Porter, LaFayette LeVan. National Decentralist Institute.
- Communism, Faculty., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Fast, Howard; Emanuel, Victor; Miller, Henry.
- Communism, Students., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Emanuel, Victor; Hoover, J. Edgar.
- Communism Miscellaneous., 1952-53 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Bienstock, Natalie; Berkner, Lloyd V.
- Communism Miscellaneous., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Communism Miscellaneous., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  DeGraff, Herrell F.; Bethe, Hans A.; Morrison, Philip; MacDonald, John W.
- Morrison Committee Records., 1951-56 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Morrison, Philip; Bache, Harold L.; Emanuel, Victor; Dean, Arthur H.; Becker, Neal Dow; Bethe, Hans A.; Wilson, Robert R.; Treman, Allan H.; Littlewood, William.
- Morrison Committee Records., 1953-54 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  DeGraff, Herrell F.; Bethe, Hans A.; Corson, Dale R.; Morrison, Philip. Subcommittee on Academic Problems Arising from Congressional Investigations.
- Morrison Committee Records., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Morrison, Philip; DeGraff, Herrell F.; MacDonald, John W.
- Morrison Committee Records., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Morrison, Philip; DeGraff, Herrell F.; MacDonald, John W.; Atwood, Sanford S.; MacLeod, R. B.; Murdock, C. C.
- Morrison Committee Records., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Morrison, Philip; DeGraff, Herrell F.; Emanuel, Victor; Farnham, William H.
- Transcript of Philip Morrison., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Morrison Committee Pamphlets., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Marcus Singer Records., 1954-59 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- J. Robert Oppenheimer., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Mimeographed Notices to Staff., 1951-53 (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
- Sympathy Letters., 1951-53 (Box 4, Folder 20-22)
- Finances, Contingency Funds., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Administrative Assistant to the President., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  McCambr idge, Robert H.
- Committee on the Size of the University. Stevens, Robert S., 1950-52 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Committee on Long Range Planning., 1951-52 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Wright, Theodore P.
- Committee on Long Range Planning., 1947-51 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Carpenter, Walter S.
- Committee on Long Range Planning., 1936-47 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Student-Administration Group Meetings., 1952-53 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Vice President for Planning and Development., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Dean, Arthur H.; Rockwell, George H.; Mar land, William H.; Alien, Laurence C.
- Vice President for Planning and Development., 1952-53 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Kaufmann, Eugene M. Office of University Development.
- Vice President for Planning and Development., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Hollister, Solomon C.; Mitchell, Albert K.; Colman, Charles C. Office of University Development.
- Vice President for Planning and Development., 1951-52 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Dean, Arthur H.; Colman, Charles C.; Murphy, Fred P.; White, Ernest I.
- Vice President for Planning and Development., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Vice President for Planning and Development., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Kane, Robert J.; McCarthy, Stephen A.
- Long-Range Planning., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- University Commission on Student Housing., 1951-53 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  Ripley, Joseph P.; Gubb, Larry E.; Upson, Maxwell M.; Treman, Robert E.; Emanuel, Victor; Ward, J. Carlton; Wade, Harry V.
- University Commission on Student Housing. Parke, John S.; Wade, Harry V., 1951-53 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- University Commission on Student Housing. Schenck, William E.; Parke, John S.; Gubb, Larry E., 1951-53 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- University Commission on Student Housing., 1951-53 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Dormitories., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Dormitories., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  Parks, John S.; Pew, Joseph N.; Morris, Evan J.; Pfann, George R.; Emanuel, Victor; Baldwin, Frank C.
- Dormitories., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  Grohmann, H. Victor.
- Request to New York State Dormitory Authority., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Contract Dining., 1951-53 (Box 4, Folder 45-47)
  Coffin, Foster M.; Arnold, Dorothy McSparran; Grohmann, H. Victor.
- Gifts Procedure, Acceptance and Acknowledgement., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 48-50)
  Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Emanuel, Victor; Palmer, Carleton H.; Taylor, Myron C.; Upson, Maxwell M.; Newman, Floyd R.; Dean, Arthur H.; Olin, John M.; Olin, Spencer T. Office of University Development.
- Cornell University Council., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Cornell University Council., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Syme, John P.
- Cornell University Council., 1952 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Gleason, James E.; Sloan, Alfred P.
- Cornell University Council., 1951-52 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Scheetz, Francis H.
- Cornell University Council., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Scheetz, Francis H.; Vonnegut, Anton; Emerson, Willard I.
- Cornell University Council., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Cornell University Medical College Dormitories., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Taylor, Edward K.; Hinsey, Joseph C.; Dean, Arthur H.; Wynn, James O.
- Parents' Program., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Cornell University Associates., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
  Kaufmann, Eugene M.; Emerson, Willard I.
- Miscellaneous Educational Matters., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Organizational Matters., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Vice President for Research., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Parmenter, Richard.
- Vice President for Research., 1952-53 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Vice President for Research., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Brookhaven National Laboratory Commitment., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Macauley, P. Stewart; Berkner, Lloyd V.; Jameson, John D. Associated Universities, Inc.
- Vice President for Business., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Burton, John E.; Wade, Harry V.; Booker, Henry G. Dining facilities.
- Dept. of Buildings and Grounds., 1952-53 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Humphreys, John W.; Parke, John S.
- Dept. of Buildings and Grounds., 1951-52 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Humphreys, John W.; Parke, John S. Day Hall flags.
- Space and Room Requirements., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Anabel Taylor Hall., 1952-53 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Butterfield, Victor L.; Taylor, Myron C.
- Anabel Taylor Hall., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Arnold, Dorothy McSparran; Grohmann, H. Victor; Taylor, Myron C.
- Anabel Taylor Hall., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 20-22)
- Safety Division., 1951-52 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Committee on Fire Prevention., 1951-52 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Barton Hall., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Teagle Hall. Teagle, Walter C. Teagle Foundation., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Statler Hall., 1950-52 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Statler, Alice.
- Moakley House., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  Kanzler, Ernest; Pew, Joseph N.
- Board on Traffic Control., 1951-52 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Sage Chapel., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Sage Chapel, Possibilities for Speakers., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Residential Halls., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Purchasing Dept., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Employment and Placement Service., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Travel and Transportation Study., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Auxiliary Enterprises., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- East Hill Airport., 1952-53 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  Peach, Robert E.; Saltonstall, Leverett. Mohawk Airlines.
- East Hill Airport., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Current Academic Budgets., 1952-53 (Box 5, Folder 39-41)
- General Instructions on Budget., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Tuition and Fees., 1950-53 (Box 5, Folder 43-45)
- Faculty Children's Tuition Exchange., 1952-53 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Veterans' Administration Billing., 1952-53 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Group Insurance., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  Gannett, Frank E.
- Contingency Funds., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Secretary of the Corporation and University Counsel., 1950-53 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  Meigs, Robert B.; Effron, Morris; Eschweiler, Alexander C.; Kaufmann, Eugene M. Buffalo Pottery, Inc.; Van Cleef residence.
- Sussman Estate. Sussman, Otto; Meigs, Robert B., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Horace White Estate., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  White, Horace.
- Maxwell M. Upson Trust., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Office of Admissions., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  Williams, Herbert H.
- Office of Admissions., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  Williams, Herbert H. Analysis of Admissions Procedure.
- Office of the Treasurer., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  Durland, Lewis H.; Dean, Arthur H.
- Quota of New Students., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Mortality Study on Admissions., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Weekly Reports on Admissions., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Applicants for Admissions., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 60-64)
  Williams, Herbert H.; Taylor, Myron C.; Storandt, Robert W.; Snickenberger, Walter A. Office of Admissions.
- Cornell Day., 1950-53 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Krieger, John A.
- Office of the University Registrar., 1950-53 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Guardabassi, Francesco Maria; Bradford, Eugene F.
- Quotas Assigned to Various Schools and Colleges., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Registration Figures., 1950-53 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Division of Unclassified Students., 1951-52 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Smith, Howard C.; Rideout, Blanchard L.
- Office of the Secretary., 1947-52 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Smith, Madge.
- Commencement Exercises., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Deans of Men and Women., 1950-52 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Alien, Lucile; Baldwin, Frank C.
- Deans of Men and Women., 1952-53 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Alien, Lucile; Baldwin, Frank C.; Reisler, Raymond; Brooks, Dorothy V. N. Committee on Student Conduct.
- Dean of Women's Position., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Alien, Lucile; Brooks, Dorothy V. N.
- Counselor of Foreign Students., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Kerr, Donald C.
- African and Egyptian students., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Policy Toward Fraternities., 1950-53 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Coyle, Harry B.; Petry, Loren C.; Pigman, James. Interf raternity Council.
- Orientation Program., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Schaffer, Robert O. Freshmen Camp.
- Advisory Committee on Orientation., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Farnham, William H.
- Student Council., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Klein, Paul L.; McDonald, John H. Labor Youth League; Cosmopolitan Club.
- Women's Self Government Association., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Abrahamson, Inger.
- Director of Veterans Education., 1952-53 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Cornell University Press., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Reynolds, Victor. Comstock Publishing Company.
- Responsibility to University Publications., 1949-52 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Hulse, M. L.
- Cornell University Library., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Mitchell, P. M.; McCarthy, Stephen A.; Bishop, Morris G.; Sabine, George H.; Emanuel, Victor. Library Associates.
- Archives and Regional History., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  Fox, Edith M.; Randall, Clarence B.; Wilder, Burt Green.
- Committee on Foreign Student and Professorial Exchange., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Television., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 24.)
  Hanna, Michael R.; Tyler, I. Keith; Moffat, Douglas M.
- Television., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Becker, Neal Dow; Gubb, Larry E.; Hanna, Michael R.; Newsom, Carroll V.; Emanuel, Victor. National Collegiate Athletic Association 1953 Television Committee; Columbia Broadcasting System.
- Visual Aids., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  Emanuel, Victor; Reynolds, Victor. Committee on Television, Radio and Sensory Aids Center; American Council on Education.
- Committee on the Economic status of the Faculty., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  MacDaniels, Laurence H.
- United States Navy Request - Committee to Study Faculty Available in the Event of a National Emergency., 1950-51 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  United States Federal Security Agency.
- Festival of Contemporary Arts., 1950-53 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  Nathan, George Jean; Kartell, John A. Committee on the Festival of Contemporary Arts.
- Committee to Study Problem of Student Morale (Student Stability)., 1950-51 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Taussig, J. Wright. Interfraternity Council; Cheating; Drinking.
- Student Values Study., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 31)
- WHCU., 1950-53 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  Hanna, Michael R.; Budd, Henry G.; Kideney, Isabel H. Federal Communications Commission.
- Photographic Science Laboratory., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Willard Straight Hall., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  Coffin, Foster M. Johnny Parson Club.
- Personnel Office., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  Willers, Diedrich K. Cornell Technical Employees Association.
- Placement Office., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  Munschauer, John L.; Gubb, Larry E. Foreign Service of the United States of America.
- Placement Office., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  Munschauer, John L.
- Placement Office - New York Office., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  Munschauer, John L.; Zalinski, Edward L. Alumni Placement Committee.
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art. Von Storch, Searle H.; Mackesey, Thomas W.; Wade, Harry V.; Dean, Arthur H.; Johnson, Herbert F.; Wright, Frank Lloyd; Parke, John S.; McConnell, James A. Buildings and Grounds Committee., 1951-52 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art., 1952-53 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  McConnell, James A.; White, Ernest I.; Taylor, Myron C.
- Andrew Dickson White Museum of Art. Kaufmann, Eugene M.; Taylor, Myron C.; Farnham, William H., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- University Faculty., 1951-52 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- University Faculty., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  Guerlac, Henry.
- University Faculty., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  Gubb, Larry E.
- Meetings., 1952-53 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  University Faculty.
- Committees of the University Faculty., 1951-52 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Pensions and Retirement., 1949-53 (Box 6, Folder 66-68)
- Salaries of Faculty., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  Priest, Alice L.; Wright, Theodore P.; Gubb, Larry E.
- Compensation for Graduate Assistants., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Terms of Appointments., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Sabbatic Leaves., 1951-53 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Endowed Professorships., 1950-53 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Scheetz, Francis H.; Eckert, Samuel B.
- New York State College of Agriculture., 1951-52 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Myers, William I.; Rumely, Edward A.; Prentice, E. Parmalee; Kurras, Bruno; Hewson, E. Wendell. New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations.
- New York State College of Agriculture. Myers, William I.; Peterson, Arthur H.; Hewson, E. Wendell; Queeny, Edgar M.; Lawrence, George H. M. United States Dept. of Agriculture., 1952-53 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- New York State College of Agriculture. Myers, William I. Farm and Home Week., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- New York State College of Agriculture Departments., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Peterson, Arthur H.; Heinicke, Arthur J. Research Club of Cornell University.
- Dept. of Agricultural Economics., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Dept. of Entomology., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Rural Science Organization., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Dept. of Rural Education., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Dept. of Agronomy., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Forestry., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Worthley, Irving T.; Hosmer, Ralph S. Yale University; Society of American Foresters.
- Mann Library., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Extension Services., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- College of Architecture., 1950-53 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Mackesey, Thomas W.; Clarke, Gilmore D.; Young, Owen D.; Wise, Charles Frederick. Association of the Alumni of the College of Architecture.
- College of Arts and Sciences., 1951-52 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Hulse, M. L.; Wade, Harry V.; Highfield, Robert; Sternglass, Lisa J.; Mineka, Francis E.; O'Leary, Paul M.
- College of Arts and Sciences., 1952-53 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Hulse, M. L.; Conable, Barber B.; Emanuel, Victor; Bald, Robert Cecil; Mineka, Francis E.; O'Leary, Paul M.
- Educational Policy Committee., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Dept. of Astronomy., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Carpenter, Martha S.
- Dept. of Chemistry., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Dept. of Economics., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Dept. of English., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Abrams, Meyer H.; Prescott, F. C.; Thompson, Harold W. New York Folklore Society.
- "Epoch11 Magazine., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Dept. of Far Eastern Studies., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Biggerstaff, Knight; Sharp, Lauriston; Kahin, George McT.; Leighton, Alexander H. American Institute of Pacific Relations; Rockefeller Foundation.
- Dept. of Geology., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Dept. of Government., 1951-52 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Einaudi, Mario; Rossiter, Clinton L.
- Dept. of History., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Coxe Literature Award., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Dept. of Mathematics., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  Draper, Glen H.; Walker, Robert J.
- Division of Modern Languages., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Cowan, J. M.
- Dept. of Music., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  Kirk, Grayson; Kirkpatrick, John I.; Rosenthal, Albert Jay; Howes, Arthur; Hull, Robert L.; Grout, Donald J.
- Bands., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  Campbell, William A.
- Chimes., 1949-52 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Dept. of Philosophy., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Dept. of Psychology., 1951-52 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  Liddell, Howard S.
- Dept. of Speech and Drama. Albright, Harry D., 1951-52 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Dept. of Sociology., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  Sharp, Lauriston; Hulse, M. L.; Holmberg, Allan R.; Leighton, Alexander H.; Myers, William I.; Mendenhall, William W. Carnegie Corporation; Cornell Southwestern Program.
- Dept. of Zoology., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Pre-Medical Committee., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- College of Engineering. Hollister, Solomon C.; Halstead, Arthur; Kimball, Dexter S.; Thurston, Robert H.; Upson, Maxwell M., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Sibley School of Mechanical Engineering., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- School of Civil Engineering., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Civil Engineering Summer Camp., 1951-52 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- School of Electrical Engineering., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- School of Chemical Engineering., 1951-52 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Geer Laboratory., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  Geer, William C.
- Graduate School of Aeronautical Engineering. Sears, William R., .1951-52 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- New York State College of Home Economics. Vincent, Elizabeth Lee., 1951-52 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- New York State College of Home Economics. Vincent, Elizabeth Lee; Failing, Jean. Farm and Home Week., 1952-53 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- New York State College of Home Economics. Vincent, Elizabeth Lee., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Recommendations for the Deanship of the New York State College of Home Economics. Myers, William I.; Blanding, Sarah Gibson; Vincent, Elizabeth Lee; Steininger, Grace; Canoyer, Helen G., 1952-53 (Box 7, Folder 49-50)
- New York State Veterinary College. Hagan, William A.; Nielsen, Selma B.; Brender, Max M. Sex discrimination; Poultry industry., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- New York State Veterinary College. Hagan, William A.; Frodin, Reuben., 1951-52 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center Joint Administrative Board. Hinsey, Joseph C.; Dean, Arthur H. New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 53-56)
- Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 57-60)
- Cornell University Medical College., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 61-66)
- Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research Annual Reports., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 67-70)
- Law School., 1951-53 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  Stevens, Robert S.; Morse, Lewis W.; MacDonald, John W.; Keeffe, Arthur J.
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Catherwood, Martin P.; Beane, A. Joynes; Hughes, Al. House Un-American Activities Committee.
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Catherwood, Martin P.; Tyler, Reese H.
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Catherwood, Martin P., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Cornell University - New York Hospital School of Nursing., 1951-53 (Box 8, Folder 4-7)
  Bayne-Jones, Stanhope; Randall, Marian G.; Becker, Neal Dow. Society of the New York Hospital; New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1952 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Franklin, Carl M. University of Oklahoma.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Litchfield, Edward H.; Schickel, Norbert H. Management Conferences.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Mann, John J.; Litchfield, Edward H.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Sawyer, Charles; Litchfield, Edward H.; Ladd, Robert D.; Emanuel, Victor; Crandall, Barrett L.
- Graduate School of Business and Public Administration., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Roswell, David S.; Bache, Harold L.; de Chazeau, Melvin G.; Bane, Frank; O'Leary, Paul M.; Litchfield, Edward H.
- School of Hotel Administration., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Meek, Howard B.; Sloan, Alfred P.; Parke, John S. Alfred P. Sloan Foundation; General Mills, Inc.; Buffalo Pottery, Inc.
- School of Hotel Administration., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Meek, Howard B.; Montesano, Michael J. Statler Foundation; Statler Hall.
- Statler Club, Hall and Plague., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Statler, Alice; Montesano, Michael J.
- School of Education., 1951-53 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Winsor, A. L.
- Teacher Training Program, School of Education., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Winsor, A. L. Fund for the Advancement of Education; Ford Foundation.
- School of Nutrition., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Gannett, Frank E.; Eastman, Edward R.
- School of Nutrition., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  Clark, Marguerite L.; Maynard, Leonard A.
- School of Nutrition., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 20-21)
  Maynard, Leonard A.; Emerson, Willard I.
- Cornell Formula Bread., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  McCay, Clive M.; Meigs, Robert B. Messing Bakeries, Inc.
- School of Nutrition., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  Vincent, Elizabeth Lee; Knowles, Asa S.; Eurich, Alvin C.
- Babcock Fund and Professorship., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  Emanuel, Victor; DeGraff, Herrell F.; Emerson, Willard I.
- Babcock Fund and Professorship., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  Emanuel, Victor; Mitchell, Albert K.; Emerson, Willard I.; McConnell, James A.
- Babcock Professorship., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  Prior, F. Weston; DeGraff, Herrell F.
- Babcock Professorship., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Babcock Professorship., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  Babcock, Howard E.
- Tuition Waivers., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Graduate School., 1951-53 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  Jones, Charles W.
- Graduate School., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  Jones, Charles W.; Sinclair, Gregg M.; Rice, C. Herbert.